A buddy murder mystery... with ghosts
Dead is a comedy, horror, mystery film directed by Hayden J. Weal.
Dane ‘Marbles’ Marbeck can see ghosts, thanks to a homemade drug: his
late father’s neurological medication mixed with marijuana.
Officer Jayson Tagg, a wannabe super-cop on the trail
of a serial killer, ends up murdered.
So when Marbles’ mum plans to sell the family farm, and the only way of buying the house off her
is taking the money offered by Tagg in exchange for his help, Marbles accepts.
The unlikely duo of stoner medium and ghost cop struggle to reconcile their differences while they navigate
their way through ghouls, perverts, a mysterious hooded figure, and an unexpected shot at love.
It becomes clear the only way Marbles and Tagg will solve the case with their souls
intact is to confront their deepest regrets and overcome their prejudices.
Ross, played by Michael Hurst.
Lloyd, played by Cameron Rhodes.
Marbles, played by Tom Sainsbury.
Janine, played by Jennifer Ward-Lealand.
Henna, played by Jess Sayer.
Tagg, played by Hayden J. Weal.
Dead Reckoning is a 2020 American action thriller
film directed by Andrzej Bartkowiak.
The film stars KJ Apa, India Eisley, Scott Adkins and James Remar.
It was released on video on demand on November 13, 2020.
The film was shot in 2016, under the original title Altar Rock.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.